dnbforum.com 2014-06-25

# Announcements - Website Feedback

> **dnbforum.com (or "Site") Privacy Policy**  
>  We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy applies to your information that we collect and receive on and through this Site; it does not apply to practices of businesses that we do not own or control or people we do not employ.
> 
> At no time will we sell or otherwise distribute your information or your personally identifiable data without your permission. You can visit this Site without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself.
> 
> By using this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use this Site and its services. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.
> 
> This Site contains links to other websites. These include links to websites that we think may be of interest to you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
> 
> **Browsing this Site**  
>  If you browse through this Site without entering any personal data, we will gather and store certain information about your visit. This information does not identify you personally and cannot be linked back to you unless you decide to identify yourself. If you are only browsing, we collect the following information: IP address, the type of browser and operating system used to access this Site, the date and time you access this Site, the pages you visit (click-through), and if you linked to this Site from another website, the address of that website as well as additional information related to your visit. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with this Site’s server, and to administer this Site.
> 
> **Information Collected**  
>  We collect the email addresses and profile information of users who register with us. We do not collect credit card information or other sensitive financial information.
> 
> All electronic communications received, either via email to non-personal addresses such as [info@dnbforum.com](mailto:info@dnbforum.com), or via the online contact system, are logged and retained for a period from the date of receipt, until such time as information is no longer needed or required by law.
> 
> All information provided by users in any of the above-listed ways or otherwise becomes the property of dnbforum.com once received and may be used and disclosed as permitted by this Privacy Policy. We may share your personal information with our affiliated companies in order to identify products or services in which you may have interest, to improve Site user experience and generally to engage in market research and for other internal business purposes.
> 
> We may use your personal information to send you email communications regarding products or services offered by us or by third parties with whom we have relationships in which we think you may be interested.
> 
> We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.
> 
> You may at any time choose not to receive promotional emails from us by changing the setting in your profile. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to this Site, as well as to facilitate, complete, or confirm any transaction that you may enter into or responding to your inquiry or request.
> 
> **Cookies**  
>  We may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a website server and stored on your computer’s hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit this Site again. Also, this Site uses cookies to track how you found this Site. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your email or any other personal data about you. To protect your privacy, we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but please be aware that if you reject our cookies it is possible that some Site pages may not properly load, your access to certain information might be denied or you might have to enter information about yourself more than once.
> 
> **Security**  
>  This Site has reasonable security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.
> 
> **Third Party Advertising**  
>  We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit this Site. These companies use non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit to this Site and other websites, such as the user IP address, pages viewed, date and time of your visit, and number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information), to serve advertisements to you on this Site and other websites that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this Site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your Internet browser.
> 
> In addition, we use clear GIFs or pixel tags to help manage our online advertising. These clear GIFs enable our advertisement serving company to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits this Site. This allows us to learn which banner advertisements bring users to this Site. The information we collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.
> 
> **Contacting this Site**  
>  Please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy on this Site, so be sure to check back here frequently.
> 
> If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you may contact us at [info@dnbforum.com](mailto:info@dnbforum.com).
> 
> dnbforum.com
> 
> Revised: 09/08/2012
